* [### Individuals
        
        Create your own booking page, set reminders, accept video meetings. Your intelligent personal assistant.](https://www.neatcal.com/for-individuals)
    * [### Classes & Courses
        
        Accept group appointments, manage recurring and one-off classes, multi-day courses & workshops.](https://www.neatcal.com/class-and-course-scheduling)
    * [### For Teams
        
        Team pages, pooled availability, round robin scheduling, collective meetings and more.](https://www.neatcal.com/for-teams)
    * [### Appointment Management
        
        Automate your scheduling rules and let neatCal take your bookings 24/7.](https://www.neatcal.com/features/appointment-management)
    * [### Website Embed
        
        Embed neatCal on your pages and let visitors schedule time without leaving your website.](https://www.neatcal.com/features/embed)
    * [### Integrations
        
        NeatCal integrates natively with virtual meeting tools (Zoom, Google Meet, Microsoft Teams), payment systems (PayPal, Stripe) and more.](https://www.neatcal.com/features/integrations)
    * [### Collective Meetings
        
        Let your customers to schedule a time to meet with multiple members of your team simultaneously.](https://www.neatcal.com/features/collective-meetings)
    * [### Compare Competitors
        
        You can find our comparisons with our competitors here.](https://www.neatcal.com/features/compare-competitors)
    * [### All Features ->
        
        See a full list of features here.](https://www.neatcal.com/features)
    
    ### Our Company

ENTR 

Privacy Policy
==============

NeatCal Privacy Policy
----------------------

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.neatcal.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
-------------------------------

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.” We collect Device Information using the following technologies: - “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit https://www.allaboutcookies.org. - “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. - “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site. Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, IBAN numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.” When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
----------------------------------------

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to: Communicate with you; Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
---------------------------------

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

INFORMATION WE RECEIVE FROM OTHER SOURCES
-----------------------------------------

Authentication Services: We allow End Users with certain third-party accounts to authenticate on the Services using those third-party accounts. We support the OAuth standard and will use the OAuth standard to facilitate End Users’ use of the Services to upload their data from their respective contact management provider whenever possible. Use of the Service with respect to third-party contact management providers that support the OAuth standard does not require neatCal to have access to, and neatCal will not in fact have access to, your End Users’ passwords in such instances. neatCal may request End Users’ credentials for certain third party contact management providers in order to complete the upload of their address book information from any source that does not support the OAuth standard. When we request this information from a third party contact management service or use the OAuth standard to facilitate authentication with a third party contact management service, we receive certain End User Content, namely registration or basic profile information from that third party service and other information that your End Users may authorize. This information enables us to authenticate the End User on that third party service and improve the Services. The information we receive depends on which contact management services the End User authorizes and any options that are available. End Users should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our Services.  
  
Third Party Analytics Services: We may also receive information from third party services to help us better understand you and how you use our Services.  
  
End Users: We also process information about our End Users, on behalf of our Users and in accordance with our user agreements. Typically, the information we receive from an End User may include the End User’s address books information, namely contact lists, contact notes, and any images associated with an End User’s address book. For clarity, neatCal only collects the minimum amount of personal data necessary for it to perform its obligations under its Terms of Service with its respective User Accordingly, any personal data about an End User is only stored in the random access memory of neatCal’s servers and never written to a physical disc. The pseudoanonymous data about an End User that remains with neatCal, is limited to a hash of each End User’s email address, the End User’s IP address, the source of the address book, and the number of contacts in the address book.

DO NOT TRACK
------------

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS
-----------

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

DATA RETENTION
--------------

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

CHANGES
-------

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US
----------

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at [\[email protected\]](https://www.neatcal.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by mail using the details provided below: Kırıkkale University - Technopark 1st Research and Development Building No: 30/27, KIRIKKALE, 71450, Turkey

Last Updated: April 15, 2020

* 
* ### Get organized, simplify admin, and grow your business.
    
* [\[email protected\]](https://www.neatcal.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
    
* Copyright © 2024 neatCal. All rights reserved.

### Product

### Industries

### Support

### Company
